多數黨黨鞭辦公室  傑奎琳·A·夏普
換了名字真不習慣
Strange not seeing your name up there.
"改變即是進步"
"To improve is to change."
"常變即是求精"
"To perfect is to change often."
很熟悉丘吉爾的名言嘛
You know your Churchill.
我離職去格蘭頓-希爾時  你送我的表上刻的
It's inscribed on a watch you gave me when I left for Glendon Hill.
是嗎  禮物的事都是南茜安排
Was it? Nancy arranges all the gifts.
她真瞭解你
She knows you well.
雖然我很喜歡跟你...
As much as I am enjoying this little --
我又爭取到兩票  帕崔奇和克勞斯
I got you two more votes. Partridge and Krauss.
雷蒙德是在向我遞橄欖枝嗎
Is this Raymond's way of extending an olive branch?
算個開端吧
It's a start.
兩票太少  算不上樹枝
Two votes is a twig. It's not a branch.
所以我來了
Which is why I'm here.
五點開始投票  還剩不到三小時
Well, the vote's at 5:00. We have less than three hours.
2小時49分鐘
Two hours and forty-nine minutes.
足夠我們拉票了
We have made more happen in less.
是我送的表嗎
Is that the watch?
不是  比那個好
No. It's nicer.
雷蒙德為什麼改主意了
So, why did Raymond have a change of heart?
政府停轉對誰都沒好處
If the government grinds to a halt, that benefits no one.
我們想讓總統專注於中國問題
We want the President focused on China,
而不是為停轉和抗議分心
not distracted by furloughs and protests.
聽傑奎琳的安排吧
You take direction from Jacqueline.
她恐怕不會喜歡那樣
She's not gonna like that very much.
不喜歡支使你嗎
Bossing you around?
不喜歡見我
Having me around.
不怪她
Oh, I don't blame her.
阿什利會先問
Ashleigh will start the interview with questions
你和丈夫的相識  早期的婚姻
about how you and your husband met, your early marriage.
好
Fine.
然後會問一些關於你近況的
Then she'll move on to more specific questions
具體問題
about your recent transition.
好的
All right.
她還要問你不要孩子的事
She's gonna ask about you having no children.
不是說好不問這個嗎
I thought we'd agreed to take that off the table.
是的  但他們一定要問
We did. But they insisted.
我可以直接找阿什利爭取
Now I can speak to Ashleigh directly and fight for --
沒事  以前也有人問過
No. It's fine. I've been asked the question before.
我知道怎麼回答
I know how to answer it.
儘可能短  不戳痛處
It'll be quick and painless.
阿什利來了我跟她確認一下
And I'll confirm that with Ashleigh when she gets here.
這件不錯
I like it.
還是別這麼中性化
Maybe something less neutral.
你穿什麼都好看
I'm sure you'll look good in whatever you choose.
我去樓下等
I'll be downstairs.
狄所裡欠你的  你幫他搞定了天橋的資金
Disori owes you -- for the overpass funding you secured.
傾向同意  中立
-沒錯    -我給他打電話
- Yes, he does.   - I'll call him.
道格呢
Where's Doug?
四處巡視  鞏固來之不易的勝利
He's doing the rounds, making sure our hard-won stay hard.
博奇和烏麥克也是  不過還是少15票
Birch and Womack are doing the same. But we're still 15 short.
我跟他們都有聯繫
Got relationships with most of these folks.
錢還不夠
Money's not enough.
我試過民主黨議會競選委員會撥款的路數了
I already tried the D-trip route.
退休問題是關鍵對吧
Retirement is the main sticking point, correct?
老人也有投票權的
Old people vote.
我去找退休人員協會  應該能減輕壓力
I'll target the AARP. That'll take most of the heat off.
這是浪費時間  我得去工作了
We're wasting our time. I gotta get to work.
帶上雷米吧
Take Remy with you.
不該分頭行動嗎
Shouldn't we divide and conquer?
兩個人更有說服力
It's harder to say "no" twice than once.
我儘量不礙事
I'll stay out of your way.
像《特拉華河流域法案》那次嗎
Like you did on the Watershed Act?
這次我們在一邊
We're on the same side of the fence this time.
你來晚了
You're late to the party.
就當雷米是你走投無路
Well, think of Remy as the guy who shows up
給你雪中送炭的人吧
with a six-pack after the liquor store is closed.
接下來見誰
Who's on your plate?
唐納德·布萊斯
Donald Blythe.
見他不浪費時間嗎
Do you really think that's the best use of your time?
除非他能說服別人
If I can get him to turn his people.
這麼多雞蛋放一個籃子裡夠冒險的
That's a lot of eggs to put in one basket.
可只有一個籃子
We only have one basket.
傑奎琳  能借用你的辦公室嗎  我比較戀舊
Uh, Jacqueline, may I use your office, for old time's sake?
全聽副總統的
I serve at the pleasure of the Vice President.
2小時17分鐘
Two hours and seventeen minutes.
有時間和耐心通常就能說服唐納德·布萊斯
Normally, all I need to sway Donald Blythe is patience and time,
可現在我兩樣都沒有
neither of which I have right now.
時間不多了
Tick, tock.
本字幕由人人影視字幕組翻譯
禁止用於任何商業盈利行為
翻譯 somehacker   癢癢   某豚   衛老哥
翻譯 盧克·天意   章魚X   喃喃
藍光版調整  timhal@HDWinG字幕組   後期 餓得慌
顧問 老杜   校對 草草   總監 草草
本字幕由YYETS翻譯 HDWinG字幕組修正 請勿去掉製作者資訊
《紙牌屋》
第二季  第四集
唐納德  你好
Donald. Good to see you.
副總統先生
Mr. Vice President.
別客氣  叫弗蘭克吧
Please, it's always "Frank" to you.
你找我  所以我來了  但我不會幫你
I came because you asked me, but don't mistake that for false hope.
抓緊時間去說服別人吧
If you have other people to lobby, you should.
十分鐘
Ten minutes.
無濟於事的
It won't change anything.
至少喝杯咖啡  反正不要錢
Well, at the very least, enjoy the free coffee.
我不喝咖啡因飲料
I don't drink caffeine.
那就脫咖啡因的
Then decaf.
那不還是咖啡因嗎
Still has caffeine.
那就享受一下免費的氧氣
Well, enjoy the free oxygen.
眾議院辦公樓那邊待久了會悶
It's gets stuffy over there in the Longworth Building.
給我來杯咖啡  然後
Coffee for me, and, uh...
氣泡礦泉水  如果你們有的話
Seltzer water, if you have it.
我們肯定有
I'm sure we do.
如果你記仇的話  我很理解
Now I can understand if you might hold a grudge.
我不記仇  弗蘭克
I don't hold grudges, Frank.
我只是不和本性虛偽的人談判
I just don't negotiate with people who are fundamentally deceptive.
我從來沒對你說過謊  唐納德
I never lied to you, Donald.
你保證說要和我討論  結果你並沒有
You promised to seek my counsel, which you never once did.
當時我們不得不把《教育法案》推到
We had to move the education bill in a direction
我知道你不會喜歡的方向上去
I knew would make you unhappy.
-我覺得不該去傷...    -你重創了工會的元氣
- I saw no reason to frustrate      - You eviscerated the unions.
你把績效標準交由聯邦統一
You federalized performance standards.
我們要是不那麼做  法案就完蛋了
If we hadn't done that, the bill would've been dead in the water.
然後現在你又想再繼續克扣你通過的那點資金
And now you want to cut the pathetic level of funding you did manage to pass.
有點錢總比沒有好吧
Isn't some funding better than none?
死了比變成植物人更能說明問題
A flat-line will send a louder message than life support.
聽著  你湊出來的這個小同盟
Look, I, I'm impressed with the little coalition
確實了不起
that you've cobbled together,
-但是我們    -也沒那麼小
- But we      - Not so little.
28票  你需要每一票
Twenty-eight votes. And you need them all.
其實一半就夠了
Well, really only half.
零的一半還是零
Half of zero is still zero.
為了讓福利改革通過參議院
I had to pull every trick in the book
我什麼手段都用了
to get entitlement through the Senate.
如果眾議院沒通過  我們沒有再來的機會
If it fails in the House, we don't get a round two.
這是一錘子買賣
This is a one-time deal.
在參議院就不該通過
It never should've passed the Senate to begin with.
我們從頭開始好嗎  我可以向你道歉嗎
Can we start over? May I offer you an apology?
我不想聽  弗蘭克  我退出了《教育法案》
Deaf ears, Frank. I withdrew myself from the education fight,
那是我必須抗下的負擔
and that is my cross to bear.
但我一個錯誤絕不會犯兩次
But I will be damned if I will make the same mistake twice.
你這麼固執  淪落到茶黨的檔次上了
This sort of stubbornness makes you no better than the Tea Party.
只不過  我們是正確的一方
Except for the fact that we happen to be right.
再坐幾分鐘  唐納德
Just a few more minutes, Donald.
你水還都沒喝呢
You haven't even had your seltzer yet.
他們在東北部還有七個資料中心
They have seven other data centers spread across the Northeast.
那希望太渺茫了吧
Those aren't good odds.
如果我們能進入一個
Well, if we can access one,
我應該就能和另七個通訊
I should be able to talk to the other seven.
它們都長那樣  像是核掩體裡的諾克斯堡
And they all look like that, Fort Knox wrapped in a nuclear bunker.
我們怎麼進去呢
How do we get in?
不是我們  是你
Well, we don't. You do.
怎麼進  我用什麼理由進
How? Wh--what's my reason?
你要寫一篇關於網路恐怖主義的文章  免費宣傳
You're writing a story on cyber terrorism. It's free publicity.
但是如果他們安保那麼嚴密
But if they're so secure, I'm --
他們經常安排參觀  主要面向潛在客戶
They give tours all the time, mostly to prospective clients.
那你自己為什麼不去呢
Then why haven't you done it yourself?
因為我開了家網路安全公司
Because I run a white-hat firm.
如果我剛參觀完  那裡就遭入侵
And if I were to show up in the tour logs before a breach,
會引起注意的
it would raise alarms.
好吧  我進去之後呢
Okay, once I'm in?
伺服器都是這個樣子的
These are what the servers look like.
你得進入隨便一個籠子裡
You're gonna get inside one of these cages.
你拿著這個  插到伺服器上
You will have this. You slide it into the server.
-就這樣    -就這麼簡單嗎
- Voila.      - It's that simple?
你要做的就這些  我可不是  程式碼極端複雜
Yeah. Well, your part. Not mine. The code's extremely complex.
我怎麼做到這些還不被他們發現呢
How do I do it without them noticing?
和想要做好任何事一樣
How you get good at anything:
熟能生巧
Practice makes perfect.
出了個狀況
We've got a problem.
所有人  停下手頭的工作  去最近的辦公室
Everyone, stop what you're doing, head into the nearest office,
把門關上
and shut the door.
你  原地不動
You, stay exactly where you are.
退休年齡已經敲定了
Retirement age is a done deal,
但我也許能撥一些款項去...
but I might be able to redistribute some appropriations to oth--
那不是我想要的
That's not what I'm after.
你不能安個新輪轂罩就當修車了
You can't fix a wrecked car with new hubcaps.
一個姊妹法案怎麼樣  完全針對教育問題
How about a sister bill, one that focuses entirely on education.
我的同盟是在為黨的尊嚴而戰
My coalition is fighting for the integrity of the party.
-我們並不是隻注重教育    -不好意思  唐納德
- Tha- We're not just focused on Education.      - I'm sorry, Donald.
稍等一下
Excuse me for a moment.
南茜  我說了  勿擾
Nancy, I said, 'No interrup'—
什麼時候
When?
但還有不到一小時就開始投票了  我
But the vote is in less than an hour. I
我才不管什麼程式
I don't care what protocol it--!
隔離  郵件中有白色粉末
Quarantine. There's white powder in the mail.
我們被關在這兒了嗎
We're locked in?
先生  馬上把門關上
Sir! Close the door now!
聽著  我必須
Look, I have to --
馬上  先生  請關門
Now, sir! Please!
我得給我夫人打電話
I should call my wife.
我也得給克萊爾打個電話
And I should call Claire.
我應該告訴康納嗎
Should I tell Connor?
不要  媒體最好不要知道
No. It's better the press doesn't know.
檢測結果應該能在投票開始之前出
The field tests should come in before the vote.
投票結束我就回家
And as soon as the tally's in, I'll come home.
情況怎麼樣
How's it looking?
挺危險  這次可能通不過
Shaky. We may lose this one.
那採訪就難辦了
That could make for a tough interview.
我本來就不想接受採訪
Well, I didn't want to do it in the first place.
現在沒法後悔了
Well, we're committed now.
我得回去應付"聖十字軍"了
I better get back to the Holy Crusader.
檢測一旦確認安全  就告訴我
Let me know as soon as the tests have cleared.
如果走運  是炭疽病毒
If we're lucky, it'll be anthrax,
我也不用親眼看著法案不通過了
and I won't live long enough to see the bill fail.
別這麼說
Don't say that.
會沒事的
We're gonna be fine.
這樣的隔離我們都經歷過多少次了
How many of these quarantines we been through?
我都算不清了
I've lost count.
祝我能勸動唐納德吧
Wish me luck with Donald.
土地爺保佑
Heels crossed.
-黨團為此四分五裂    -當然
- It's ripping the caucus apart.   - Of course.
我們要一起堅持用我們這版法案
We take a united stand on our version of the bill.
我們有些人得立場堅定
Some of us have to stay on our feet.
事關黨內團結
This is about party unity...
這是讓我們放棄根基
It's about abandoning our base.
不  凍結開銷才是動搖根基
No, that's what the Freeze is.
刀兵相向對我們的根基沒什麼好處
Our base doesn't benefit from sword-rattling.
只會搞得烏煙瘴氣
It gets left bleeding on the field.
我的選區內的老年人數目在國內第三多
My district has the third largest number of seniors in the country.
如果提高退休年齡  退休人員協會得吵翻天的
If we raise the age of retirement, the AARP will raise hell.
我今早和退休人員協會的主席談過
I spoke with the President of the AARP this morning.
他下週將收到一筆4500萬的捐款
He'll be receiving a $45 million endowment next week.
選民還是會抗議的
Voters will still revolt.
中期選舉結果不會好看
The midterms are gonna be ugly.
弗蘭克·安德伍德  國會封鎖  我困在這兒了
我們很多人  當然也包括我...
Many of us – And I can certainly speak for myself – are fac --
現在的選擇是  政府立刻停擺
The choice is between immediate discontinuation of services
或是五年後提高退休年齡
and an age bump five years from now.
你是在拿假想的不適跟眼前的痛苦相比
You're comparing theoretical discomfort to imminent pain.
我只是覺得我們在跟核心價值觀背道而馳
I just feel like we're losing touch with our core values.
《教育法案》就是個很好的例子
The Education Bill is a good example.
我們跟著弗蘭克走
We all followed Frank's lead,
希望能靠他多少牽制一下共和黨
hoping it would buy us traction with the Republicans.
失陪一下  馬上回來
Would you excuse me, just one moment?
-媒體知道了嗎    -還不知道
- Does the press know?   - Not yet.
能和他保持聯繫嗎
Can you keep in touch with him?
我得想辦法讓午餐賓客從命
I need to pommel our lunch guests into submission.
你已經很接近了  放輕鬆  多聽
You've got 'em close. But relax. Listen more.
他們想要的是支援  而不是打擊
They want their hands held, not someone in their face.
我知道怎麼拉票
I know how to whip votes.
請享用特區最好的魚子醬  女士們先生們
Best caviar in D.C., Ladies and Gentlemen.
我們怎麼能讓你付錢
We can't let you pay for that.
那就別吃  如果吃了我也不會透露出去
Then don't eat it. But if you do, I won't tell anyone.
你剛剛說到《教育法案》是嗎
You were saying about the Education Bill?
不  馬喬裡親愛的
No, Marjory, honey.
記得嗎  我們剛剛才說過
Remember, we just talked about it.
我剛剛在說...
I was telling you –
對  沒什麼好擔心的
Right. Nothing to worry about.
如果有什麼疑問  就去問莫里
If you have any questions, ask Molly.
她知道怎麼回事
She knows what's going on.
我知道任何訊息就會馬上聯繫你
I will call as soon as I know anything.
我愛你
I love you.
馬喬裡怎麼樣
How's Marjory?
她還好
She's okay.
電話打得挺長
Long call.
你也知道  她情緒比較激動
You know, she gets emotional.
莫里休學了一個學期待在家裡
Molly took a semester off to be at home.
我告訴她  春季必須回去
I told her she needs to head back in the spring.
我不希望她媽媽拖她後腿
I don't want her mother dragging her down.
你真是不容易
Must be hard on you.
我覺得女兒們更不容易
Harder on the girls, I think.
-她意識清醒嗎    -一半時間是吧
- Is she lucid?   - About half the time.
勉強能明白自己惡化得多快
Just enough to be aware of how quickly she's going.
真糟糕
Awful.
我知道我不該這麼說
I feel terrible saying it,
但我心底更希望她別清醒過來
but part of me is looking forward to her not being lucid.
至少那樣她就不會知道發生了什麼
At least then she won't realize what's happening.
我之前就該想到的
I should have thought of this before.
將心比心  而不是靠講道理
Appeal to the heart, not the brain.
我對這方面不太瞭解  但
Forgive my ignorance, but
這方面的研究有什麼進展嗎
has there been any progress with research?
一些  基因測試  血管改造  但進展很慢
Some. Genetic testing, vascular manipulation, but it's slow.
馬喬裡趕不上這些研究的成果了
They won't come up with anything in time for Marjory.
所以我們只想提高生活質量
We're focusing on quality of life.
聽著  我知道你還有事  我...
Look, I -- I know you have work to do, so...
我已經不是黨鞭了  那是傑奎琳的工作
Oh, I'm no longer the Whip anymore. That's Jacqueline's job.
我同意見你  是因為我們有交情
I just agreed to meet with you because we have a history.
她很難拒絕吧
She would be tougher to say not to.
-但還是該拒絕的    -沒錯
- But still it would've been a "no".   - Yes.
我佩服你的信念  唐納德
I admire your convictions, Donald.
如今像你這樣的人鳳毛麟角了
You're a rare breed nowadays.
你拿我們跟茶黨比的時候  可不是這麼說的
It didn't sound that way when you were comparing us to the Tea Party.
我不該那麼說
I was being unfair.
你不是反動派  是進步分子
You're not a reactionary. You're a progressive.
我明白你的意思
I see where this is going.
什麼意思
How do you mean?
我坐了這麼久冷板凳
When you've been in the wasteland as long as I have,
對奉承已經有免疫力了
you become immune to flattery.
我知道你認為我是個本性虛偽的人
I know you think I'm fundamentally deceptive,
但我也能真誠地讚美別人
but I am capable of a genuine compliment.
那我就謝謝你了  但這不會動搖我的決心
Then I will take it as one, but it won't soften my resolve.
當然  否則你就配不上這讚美了
If it did, you wouldn't deserve the compliment in the first place.
如果你投了反對票  我也不會指責你們
If you vote ':no,' I won't hold it against you.
我們一條陣線的  中期選舉也是
We're all in this together through the midterms.
但如果你們跟我走
But if you stick with me,
我們就讓共和黨和美國人民知道
we can show both the Republicans and the American people
我們不是就會鬧僵
that we are capable of more than stagnation.
這是很重要的  就算會有些痛苦
And that's worth something, even it if hurts.
你們誰跟我走
Who can I count on?
收到
Copy that.
我們之間還隔著道門  我猜不是好兆頭
The fact that there is still a door between us, I take as a bad sign.
一份樣本檢測呈陰性  一份不確定  先生
One tested negative, one inconclusive, sir.
所以我們必須把樣本帶回實驗室
That means we have to take the samples to the lab.
那還要多久
So, how much longer?
還需要三四個小時吧
Another three or four hours.
我們有一項重要投票要舉行
We have an important vote going to the floor.
我必須跟我的人談談
I have to be talking to my people.
投票已經延期了  先生
The vote is delayed, sir.
我們正在疏散國會大廈這一側
We're evacuating this side of the Capital.
不投票了嗎
So no vote?
在我們確認沒問題之前不會投票了
Not until we get the all-clear.
好人有好報
Good things happen to good people.
還有一件事  先生
Another thing, sir.
所有的手機服務  無線網  座機
All cell phone service, Wi-Fi, land lines --
我們都會封鎖  以防可能安全威脅
We'll be blocking them, in case there's a legitimate security threat.
我得跟我妻子保持聯繫
I need to be able to call my wife.
抱歉  先生  我們可以找人通知她
I apologize, sir. We can have someone notify her.
不  必須是我才行
No. It needs to be me.
如果是陌生的聲音  會讓她非常緊張
She gets very anxious if she doesn't recognize the voice.
議員先生  我被嚴令禁止...
Congressman, I have strict instructions not to allo—
想辦法解決  除非你想讓我把白宮扯進來
Figure it out. Unless you want me to get the White House involved.
我會想辦法的  先生
I'll find a way, sir.
當副總統還是有好處的
There are advantages to being Vice President.
女士  我們得要求你暫時留在這裡
Ma'am? We'll have to ask you to remain up here for a little while.
是因為隔離嗎
Is it the quarantine?
國會大廈正在疏散
The Capitol is being evacuated.
應該不會有問題
We expect everything to be fine.
只是標準程式
It's just standard procedure.
你打不通的  通訊中斷了
Uh, you won't be able to get through. Communication is being jammed.
我沒法跟弗蘭西斯通話嗎
You mean I can't even speak to Francis?
確認安全之前不行
Not until the all-clear.
要多久
How long?
現在估計要四小時
Four hours is the estimate right now.
25分鐘後就要錄影了
We're supposed to tape it in 25 minutes.
我們無能為力
Nothing we can do.
你還好嗎
You okay?
是的
Yes.
我去找艾瑪談談
I'll go talk to Emma.
沒事了  謝謝你
You know, I'm fine. Thank you.
艾瑪
Em.
我們可能有點問題
So we might have a problem.
新聞裡都報道了
It's all over the news.
可能還要一陣子
It could be a while.
我們能通過音訊採訪副總統嗎
Can we get audio from the Vice President?
在疏散結束之前通訊都是中斷的
Communications are being jammed until the evacuation is over.
你跟阿什利談過了嗎
Have you spoken to Ashleigh?
她覺得我們該弄輛轉播車來  回頭直播
She thinks we should get a sat truck down here. Wait and go live.
我沒法保證什麼時候能恢復
I can't guarantee when that will be.
副總統被隔離在國會大廈  我們有獨家新聞
The Vice President is quarantined in the Capitol, and we have an exclusive.
不管我們何時開工  電視臺都會轉播的
The network will broadcast whenever the hell we tell them to.
他們會等你到達
They're holding off until you get here.
你應該獨自做採訪
You should do the interview solo.
我想等你
I'd rather wait.
誰知道我們能不能贏得投票
Who knows whether we'll win the vote?
如果我們輸了
If we lose,
我可不想上全國電視臺
I don't want my face on national television.
這或許也是好事
This could be a silver lining.
我不知道  弗蘭西斯
I don't know, Francis.
你肯定會很棒的
I'm sure you'll be terrific.
我跟康納商量一下吧
Let me run it past Connor.
好的  謝謝  我們說完了
Okay. Thank you. We're done.
先生  我們接通了布萊斯太太
Sir, we were able to get Mrs. Blythe.
唐納德
Oh, Donald...
馬喬裡
Marjory?
-喂    -對  是我  親愛的
- Hello?   - Yes, it's me, sweetheart.
聽不清你說話
It's hard to hear you.
我們還被困在辦公室裡
We're still stuck inside the office.
什麼辦公室
What office?
在國會大廈  還得要一陣子
At the Capitol. It --it's going to be a l—a little while longer.
但你為什麼去那裡  今天是星期天啊
But why are you there? It's Sunday.
不  今天是星期五  親愛的
No, it -- it's Friday, sweetheart.
-唐納德    -我在呢
- Donald?   - I'm here.
跟我在一起的男人是誰
Uh, who is this man with me?
他是一位警察
Uh, he's a police officer.
他們用對講機讓我們通話
They're using walkie-talkies so we can speak.
我在跟誰說話
Who am I talking to?
是您丈夫  夫人
It's your husband, ma'am.
我沒結婚
I'm not married.
是我  是唐納德
It -- It's me. It's Donald.
關上  我不認識那個那人
Turn it off. I don't know that man.
馬喬裡
Marjory...
她去另一個房間了  先生
She went into the other room, sir.
好的  謝謝
Okay. Thank you.
能麻煩你陪著她嗎
If you could stay with her, please...
好的  先生
Yes, sir.
喝一杯嗎
Drink?
好啊
Sure. Why not?
他可能要到午夜才有空
For all we know it could be midnight before he's out.
然後他還要主持投票
And then he still needs to manage the vote.
凌晨兩點我們也沒問題
We're fine if it's two a.m.
大家都睡著的時候播嗎
When everyone's asleep?
人們會為這個熬夜的
People would stay up for this.
關鍵就是想在黃金時段播
The whole point was prime time.
那我們明天再進行
Then we do it tomorrow.
我們已經為這個推掉半天的日程了
We've already set aside half a day for this.
副總統先生不會為一個訪談重新安排一整天的日程
The Vice President can't rearrange his entire schedule for an interview.
眼下也沒有其他的選擇
I don't see any other options.
我和弗蘭西斯用對講談過了
I spoke to Francis over the radio.
我們認為應該我單獨接受採訪
We think I should do it alone.
只有你一人
Just you?
安德伍德夫人和阿什利  一對一
Mrs. Underwood and Ashleigh, one-on-one.
也許我們可以轉播他的錄音
Maybe we can broadcast his voice
弗蘭西斯不希望訪談完全是關於隔離的
Francis doesn't want the entire interview to be about the quarantine.
我也一樣  那隻是個小插曲
Neither do I. That's just spectacle.
隔離是新聞  這是難得的機會
The quarantine is news. We have a unique opportunity --
那好  我們取消吧
Fine. We're done.
-什麼    -取消訪談  不重新安排
- What?      - Cancel the interview. No reschedule.
別這樣  康納
Come on, Connor.
請你收拾好東西離開
Please pack up everything and leave.
好吧  我給阿什利打電話
Okay, wait. Let me call Ashleigh.
我以為我會逐漸習慣
I thought I'd get used to it,
但我沒有  每次還是很痛苦
but no. Hurts every time.
你和一個人一起生活了三十年
You spend 30 years with someone,
而現在她甚至不知道你是誰
and then they don't have a damn clue who you are.
我真的不應該
Ugh... I really shouldn't...
如果我們不該做的事就不做
If we never did anything we shouldn't do,
那就體會不到做該做的事的成就感了
we'd never feel good about doing the things we should.
說的好
Excellent point.
如果這是我們生命最後的時刻
And if these are our last moments on earth
我不知道你怎麼打算  我倒寧願喝醉了
I don't know about you, but I'd rather go out with a buzz on.
敬馬喬裡
To Marjory.
你非常愛她
You love her dearly.
勝過其他一切
More than anything.
我不敢想像沒有克萊爾我會怎麼辦
I can't imagine what I'd do without Claire,
或是如果她記不起我是誰
or if she didn't remember who I was.
但願你不會遇到這樣的情況
Hopefully, you'll never have to.
可你  或是任何人遇上這種事都讓我覺得生氣
Well, it makes me angry that you do, that anybody does.
沒必要為你不能改變的事而生氣
No sense being angry over what you can't change.
老年癡呆的研究有多少經費
How much funding does Alzheimer's research get?
不到五億
Just under $500 million.
我不是專家  但這個數聽上去有點少啊
Well, I'm no expert, but that sounds inadequate to me.
確實是  如果分配一百塊用於研究
It is. For every $100 we allocate to research,
就得花將近三萬用於看護
we spend nearly $30,000 on care.
得改變這種情況
We oughta change that.
我試過了  我的法案都沒通過委員會
I tried. My bill didn't even leave committee.
誰反對
Who opposed it?
霍華德·韋伯
Howard Webb.
撥款委員會的
Ugh. Appropriations.
他都沒讓法案投票
He didn't even put it to a vote.
我向來不喜歡霍華德
I've never been fond of Howard.
我也一樣
That makes two of us.
他的原因是什麼
What was his argument?
他覺得他不欠我的
He didn't feel he owed me one.
"浪費開銷"  他就說了這一句
'Fiscally irresponsible,' is all he said.
跟我好好說說你的法案
Walk me through the specifics of your bill.
我知道你要幹什麼了
I see what you're doing.
幹什麼
Doing what?
你真讓人噁心  弗蘭克
You're disgusting, Frank.
你說什麼
Excuse me?
利用我妻子
Using my wife.
唐納德  你在說什麼
Donald, what are saying?
你以為你多給老年癡呆一點研究經費
You think I'll give in on Entitlement
我就會在福利改革修正案上妥協
if you slap some extra Alzheimer's funding on the table?
我完全沒這個意思
I was not suggesting that at all.
胡說  弗蘭克
Bullshit, Frank.
你可以隨便看低我
You think as little of me as you want,
但我不拿健康作交易籌碼
but I do not barter with people's health.
那你為什麼要上調退休年限
Then why are you trying to raise the age of Retirement?
醫療研究  我們負擔得起
Medical research we can afford.
醫療保險  我們負擔不起  這是現實  唐納德
Medicare, we can't. There are realities, Donald.
別和我談什麼現實  我妻子在漸漸死去
Don't talk down to me about reality. My wife is dying.
這才是現實  如果你的法案通過
That's a reality. Other people will die, too,
還有其他人會死  這才是現實
if your package succeeds. That's a reality.
該死的
God damn it.
真希望我沒跟你一起困在這兒
I wish I wasn't stuck in this fucking room with you.
唐納德
Donald?
我不想再說什麼了
I'm done talking.
-再來一次    -我能行
- One more time.   - I've got it.
我希望聽起來更自然
I want it to sound more natural.
弗蘭西斯和我獻身公共事業
Uh, Francis and I both wanted to devote our lives to public service.
而我們一致認為投身公職
And we didn't feel that we could both do that
就難以善盡父母之責
and be the parents we wanted to be.
所以我們作了取捨  讓我們有更多時間
And by making that choice it allows more time for us
為其他人服務
to be in the service of others.
很好  聽起來很好
Good. That sounds good.
請過來吧  安德伍德夫人
We need you, Mrs. Underwood.
讓德里克待在國會大廈
Keep Derek at the Capitol.
採訪被疏散者和國土安全部
I want quotes from evacuees and Homeland Security.
讓薩拉完成生化威脅歷史的部分
And Sarah should be finishing that history of biohazard scares.
我很快就過去
I'll be there soon.
我要走了
I have to go.
不行  我們還沒幹完
No. We're not done yet.
這是個大新聞  我明天再過來
This is a major story. I'll come back tomorrow.
那樣你就是連續兩天都是如此  這就有了規律
Gonna be two days in a row, and this is how patterns emerge.
聯調局喜歡規律  我們不能去撞槍口
The FBI likes patterns, and we do not give the FBI what the FBI likes.
我不能一整天都消失  現在正是...
I can't disappear all day in the middle of –
我有八個記者正在外面跑新聞
I have eight reporters out in the field,okay?
別說了
Stop.
告訴我  我為什麼要買腰果
Tell me why I purchased Cashew.
我不知道
I don't know.
為了陪伴我嗎
Companionship?
是的
Yes.
更重要的是  提醒我自己
More importantly, a reminder that I am never
我距離被關進籠子裡只有一步之遙
more than one wrong move away from life in a cage.
你留下來
You stay.
我讓你看看我要寫的全部程式碼
I'll walk you through every line of code I intend to write,
我每一次對防火牆的攻擊
every attempt I make to breach the wall.
如果我們被抓  你不能說自己一無所知
If we get caught, you don't get to plead ignorance.
我們一起進去
We go down together.
不  我不是來玩雌雄大盜的
No, I didn't sign up for Bonnie and Clyde.
你需要我做這一件事
You need me for this one thing.
我也需要你  但無論我來之前你做了什麼
Just like I need you. But whatever you've done before me, that --
你知道我住在哪裡  你知道我是誰
You know where I live. And you know who I am.
坐下  我們越早開始  就能越早結束
Sit down. The sooner we start, the sooner we finish.
國會大廈依然封鎖  防化部隊成員
The Capitol is still on lockdown, as HAZMAT crews
還在繼續檢查整棟大廈
continue a thorough sweep of the building.
今天早上  一封寄給多數黨黨鞭
Earlier this morning, a white powder-like substance...
傑奎琳·夏普的包裹中
...was found in a package mailed to the office
發現了白色粉末狀物質
of Majority Whip Jacqueline Sharp.
我們現在可以走了嗎
Not are we free to go?
快了  不到一小時
Almost, sir. Less than hour.
我有一條你太太發來的訊息
I've got a message from your wife.
什麼訊息
What is it?
她正在做現場採訪
She's doing the interview live right now.
與議員唐納德·布萊斯及夏普女士手下
...Quarantined with Congressman Donald Blythe
十四名員工隔離在一起  特情局...
and 14 of Miss Sharp's staff. The secrets
安德伍德夫人  我非常感激你
Mrs. Underwood, I so appreciate you taking the time to speak
能在今天這種情況下與我們對話
with us today in what, I am certain,
你現在一定很擔心
is a very stressful situation.
謝謝  阿什利
Thank you, Ashleigh.
你今天跟你丈夫通過話嗎
Have you spoken with your husband today?
是的  他狀態很不錯
Yes, I did. And he's in very good spirits,
特情局處理的很好
and in good hands with the Secret Service.
當然  對於不能來他感到很失望
Of course, he's very disappointed he couldn't be here.
我們的心與他同在
Well, our thoughts are with him and --
以及被隔離在國會大廈的所有人
and everyone quarantined at the Capitol.
謝謝你
Thank you.
我想要你在德克薩斯州
I'd like to begin with Claire Underwood
遇到你丈夫之前開始說起
before she met her husband, in Texas.
我有一些照片
And I have a couple of pictures.
-不會吧    -是的
- Oh, no.   - Yes.
天吶  那是紅鬃
Oh. My goodness. That was Red.
你是個熟練的騎手嗎
An accomplished rider?
狂熱的騎手
Uh, an enthusiast.
這張是幾年以後的照片
This one's from a couple of years later.
天吶
Oh, my goodness.
你喜歡這雙皮便鞋嗎
You like those penny loafers?
妙極了
Those are wonder—
這是兩個截然不同的女孩
Those are two very different girls.
你更喜歡做哪一個
Which one are you more comfortable being?
我家的農場  那是我的家園
My family's ranch. That was home…for me.
你不喜歡預科學校嗎
You didn't like the prep school?
不  我想我更喜歡泥巴
No. I think I preferred the dirt.
但你在達拉斯長大  在高地公園
You grew up in – in Dallas, though. Um, Highland Park.
是的  我父親  他是個生意人
Yes. My father, um, well, he was a businessman,
所以我們住在城裡  但我們是農場主
So we lived in the city, but we're ranchers.
我們家過去三代人都是
I mean, we – we go back three generations, our family.
你父母非常有錢
Your parents were very wealthy.
我們過得很舒坦  沒錯
Uh, we were comfortable, yes.
他們讓我應有盡有
They made sure I wanted for nothing.
的確是個快樂的童年
It was a very happy childhood.
那段時間你最鮮活的記憶是什麼
What is your most vivid memory from that time?
我"最鮮活的記憶"
My 'most vivid memory.'
可能是我九歲或十歲的時候
Probably when I was about nine or ten,
我父親帶我去了肯尼迪遇刺的迪利廣場
my father took me to Dealey Plaza, where Kennedy was shot.
他說"克萊爾  一位偉人死在這裡"
And he said, 'Claire, a great man died here.'
我記得我當時還不完全理解死亡的概念
And I remember not fully comprehending the meaning of death yet.
我問他總統怎麼死的  他就跟我說了
And I asked him how he died, and he told me.
我記得我感到十分難過和憤怒
And I remember feeling so sad, so angry.
這太不公平了
It seemed so unfair.
我哭了起來  然我後父親抱起我
I started to cry, and my daddy picked me up.
他用胳膊摟著我
And he wrapped his arms around me,
然後說道  "別傷心  寶貝兒
and he said, 'Don't be sad, sweetheart.
他讓世界變得更好了
"He made the world a better place,
但有時這是要付出代價的"
but sometimes that comes at a price.'
我想這就是我最鮮活的記憶了
I guess that was the most vivid memory.
我們就差八票了
We are only eight votes away.
抱歉  我心意已決
I'm sorry. I've made up my mind.
我也一樣  我得堅持立場
Me, too. I've gotta stick to my guns on this one.
你們寧願讓政府關門...
You would rather let the government shut down --
你注意點
Hey, hey, hey.
這你怨不著我們
Don't put that on us
誰叫黨鞭大人最後才想起來我們
just because we're on the ass-end of the whip list.
別誤會  我們都很敬重你  傑姬
Don't get us wrong. We have a lot of respect for you Jackie.
弗蘭克升任之後你一直幹得不錯
You're doing a fine job since Frank's gone.
也許風格不同  但還是很好的
Different styles, but a fine job.
請諸位稍候片刻
Excuse us just a moment.
他們根本不拿我當回事
They're not taking me seriously.
因為你不是弗蘭克
'Cause you're not Frank.
你是說我不是個男人
You mean because I'm not a man.
不  我就是說弗蘭克  他們都習慣了做交易
No. I mean Frank. They're used to being offered something.
問問他們有什麼要求
Ask them what they want.
我知道保羅在垃圾處理廠的事上需要幫忙
I know Paul needs help with a waste treatment facility.
你也和他們一樣瞧不起我
You're being just as condescending as they are.
有好建議送到眼前  就接受吧
Take some good advice when you get it.
我之前就說對了  是不是
I was right earlier, wasn't I?
保羅  雷米告訴我你需要一間垃圾處理廠
Paul, Remy tells me you need a waste treatment plant.
我們在申請聯邦基金方面是有點麻煩
We've had some trouble getting matching federal funds.
本  你說你想在選區裡蓋一座葡萄酒博物館
Ben, you mentioned once a winery museum in your district?
我們長島如今的葡萄酒是很不錯
We are making some great wines in Long Island these days.
我喝過啊
I've tried some.
跟納帕[著名酒鄉]產的比起來難喝得要死
It tastes like piss, compared to what we have in Napa,
這種東西正好該送進保羅的垃圾處理廠
the sort of piss that belongs in Paul's waste treatment plant.
傑姬
Jackie--
我們剛遭遇了一場疑似恐怖襲擊
We have a possible terror attack,
而你們還在這持票待沽
and you're holding out your plate for more pork.
你們真該為自己感到羞愧
You should be ashamed of yourselves.
我治下黨團  黨員只會因優異表現受嘉獎
In my caucus, people are rewarded for good behavior,
我不會鼓勵拿選票換酬金
not trading their votes for ransom.
待會兒進去投票  你們兩位都要投贊成
When we walk in there, I expect the both of you to vote 'yes,'
而且要毫不猶豫
without a moment's hesitation.
多謝兩位心意回轉
Thank you for your change of heart.
只剩六票了
Six more to go.
你離開德州  在著名的菲利普斯學院
You left Texas and, um, spent the last two years of high school
度過了中學最後兩年
at the prestigious Phillips Academy.
然後考進了拉德克利夫學院
Um, and then, onto Radcliffe. Yes.
哈佛大學兩個本科生院之一  專收女生
就是在那兒  你邂逅了未來的美國副總統
Where you would meet the future Vice President.
他那時只是個帥氣的法學院學生
Back then just a dashing law student.
我從沒想到過他會成為副總統
I never dreamed he would become Vice President, of course.
有人認為你們的婚姻比你說的要
Some people might think that your marriage may be a bit more
有更多的算計
calculated than you let on,
也許他用得上你家的財富
that perhaps he needed your family's money.
不  不是這樣的
No. That's just not true.
你父親可是為他的競選投入不菲
Your father did contribute an awful lot to his campaign.
沒錯  因為他相信弗蘭西斯
Yes, he did. Because he believed in Francis.
如果沒有你父親的資助
Would he have won that campaign
他還能贏得選舉嗎
had it not been for your father's contributions?
這我不清楚  我父親的資助絕對起了作用
I don't know. I mean, it certainly helped.
但我認為  是弗蘭西斯的理念和領導力
But I like to think that it was Francis' ideas and leadership
說服了選民  而不僅僅是競選廣告
that convinced voters, not just TV commercials.
你和副總統已結婚27年了
You've been married for 27 years.
是的
That's right.
你們結婚時還在上學  那時你們都很年輕
You were just in school. I mean, you married so young.
沒錯  但如果找到了真愛
We did. But when you've found 'the one'…
弗蘭西斯就是我的真愛
well, Francis was the one.
你稱呼他為"弗蘭西斯"
You call him "Francis."
在老家  他們還是叫他"弗蘭克"
Well, back home, they call him "Frank," still.
但他喜歡我叫他"弗蘭西斯"
But he likes that I call him "Francis."
他說這稱呼讓他顯得更老成
He said it makes him sound more sophisticated.
當政治家的妻子難嗎
Is it hard being a politician's wife?
令人興奮  但也有難處
It's thrilling. Not without its challenges.
甘居幕後  為了他的追求而委屈自己
Always in the background, subsuming your goals for his goals.
我倒不這麼看
No, I don't see it that way.
我們都是非常獨立的人
We're two very independent people who
只是選擇共同經營生活而已
have chosen to live our lives together.
我支援他 他也支援我
I support him. He supports me.
這就回到了政治上的合作的話題上
Which, you know, goes back to the political partnership.
我丈夫的確是位政治家
Well, my husband happens to be a politician,
而我也正好從事政治工作
and I happen to do political work.
但我們的關係遠不止如此
But our partnership extends far beyond that.
孩子呢  這是你們做的犧牲嗎
Children. Was that a sacrifice?
因為你們還沒生過孩子
Because you haven't had any.
弗蘭西斯和我獻身公共事業
Francis and I wanted to devote our lives to public service.
而我們一致認為投身公職
And we didn't feel that we could both do that
就難以善盡父母之責
and be the parents we wanted to be.
所以我們作了取捨
So, we made the choice.
這回答我們之前聽過了
We've heard that answer before.
你說什麼
Sorry?
你在以前的訪問中給出過一模一樣的回答
You have given the exact same answer in previous interviews.
因為這是事實
Because it's the truth.
不好意思  但是"工作"和"時機"
Forgive me, but 'career' and 'timing,'
人們總會找這樣的藉口
uh, those are often very convenient answers.
從有這個念頭到真正去做之間有個過程
It is true that whatever it takes for people to get
而我一直沒能走完這個過程
from 'maybe' to 'yes' never arrived for me.
你不覺得有壓力嗎  沒有做母親的渴望嗎
Never felt the pressure? No maternal instinct?
沒有
No.
那麼這是你的選擇  並不是你不能生育
And it was a choice? It wasn't because you couldn't have any?
弗蘭西斯和我是為了大局著想
Well, Francis and I did what was right for us.
因為即使是現在
Because it is unusual, I mean, even now,
身在領導層的政治家沒有孩子
for politicians at the executive level
也是不尋常的事
not to have children.
是的
Yes, it is.
你丈夫第二次參加國會競選時
In your husband's second congressional campaign,
有一位反墮胎的共和黨候選人
there was a Republican, a pro-family candidate,
他對你們做了一些相當難聽的指責
who made some pretty unsettling accusations.
弗蘭西斯是一位南方的民主黨人
Well, Francis is a Southern Democrat,
我倆的臉皮都很厚
and we have thick skins.
他說  為了保住你丈夫的政治生涯
He suggested, in order to keep your husband's political career on track.
孩子是很多人生活的中心
Children are the center of many people's lives.
我認為他們只是想確保
And I think they just want to make sure that
選出的代表會為了他們孩子的未來奮鬥
their representatives will fight for their children's dreams.
而弗蘭西斯已經一次又一次地證明了自己
And Francis has, again and again, proven that he will.
作為副總統他也會繼續做出努力
And he will continue to do as Vice President.
他還聲稱在競選時你可能已經懷孕
He claimed that you may have been pregnant during the campaign.
你當時懷孕了嗎
Was there a pregnancy?
你懷過孕嗎
Have you ever been pregnant?
-馬上停播    -不行
- Break. Now.   - That's not gonna happen.
懷過
Yes.
在競選期間嗎
During the campaign?
之前
Before.
是流產了嗎
Was it a miscarriage?
不是
No.
你終止妊娠了嗎
Did you – did you terminate the pregnancy?
如果我說"是"
If I said 'yes,'
我丈夫的政治生涯就會面臨危險
my husband's political career would be in jeopardy.
我信仰會遭質疑
My faith would be questioned.
同樣  我的生活也會受到威脅
Likely, my life would be threatened.
但我不會感到羞恥  是的  我懷過孕
But I won't be ashamed. Yes, I was pregnant.
而且是的  我墮過胎
And, yes, I had an abortion.
能休息幾分鐘嗎
Can you excuse me for one moment?
當然可以  稍後繼續為您帶來
Of course. We'll have more of our live interview
與克萊爾·安德伍德的直播訪談
with Claire Underwood when we return.
那可需要極大的勇氣
That took a lot of guts.
是啊
Yes, it did.
不行  那看上去像是我羞於啟齒
No. It'll look like I am ashamed.
但我沒有  我也不會
I'm not. And I won't.
你再怎麼說都無法挽回
Nothing you can say will make this any better.
我寧願去解決麻煩...
I'd rather deal with the dama--
我不會逃避這個問題
I'm not going to run from this.
她會問你為什麼要墮胎
She's gonna ask why you had the abortion.
不止一次  是三次
I haven't had one. I've had three.
三次  不行  你必須堅稱只有一次
Three? No. You need to stick to one.
好吧
Okay, fine.
告訴我你要說什麼
Tell me what you'll say.
我不能說出真相
Well, I can't use the real reason.
前兩次我還未成年  我做事不顧後果
The first two, I was a teenager, and I was reckless.
那第三次呢
What about the third?
那篇她給我看的文章寫得沒錯
Well, the article that she showed, it's right.
我當時在吃避孕藥
I was on the pill.
但沒有起效果
It didn't work.
我們討論過要小孩  最終決定不要了
We talked about having a baby, and then we decided against it.
為什麼
Why?
因為我們在專心忙競選的事
Because we were focused on the campaign.
懷孕多少個星期了
How many weeks in?
16周
Sixteen.
這些你絕不能說
You can't say any of this.
上樓去  我來應付阿什利
Go upstairs. I'll deal with Ashleigh.
如果要繼續的話  還有20秒就開始了
If we're going to continue, we've got about 20 seconds.
康納  我
Connor, I --
請相信我  不然你會犯大錯的
Please, trust me. You'll be making a big mistake.
你願意談談當時的情況嗎
Are you willing to discuss the circumstances --?
我的懷孕是一次性侵害造成的
I became pregnant as a result of a sexual assault.
你是說你被
Are you saying that you – you were --?
強姦了
Raped.
你之前從沒公開說過這件事
You've never spoken about this publicly about this before.
沒有人過問
No one ever asked.
你能講講發生了什麼嗎
Can you tell us what happened?
是上大學的時候  一個在和我約會的同學
Uh, it was college. A classmate, we were dating.
發生在...有一次我們吵架了
And it happened on a – We had a fight,
然後他強暴了我
and he forced himself on me.
你和別人說過這件事嗎  他被起訴了嗎
Did you tell anybody about it, and did he --? Was he charged?
沒有  因為當時我覺得錯似乎在我身上
No. Because at the time I felt that I was somehow at fault.
我知道我沒錯
I knew I wasn't,
但我不想被別人指指點點
but... just didn't want to be stared at.
我不想別人叫我"被強暴的女孩"
I didn't want to be known as 'the girl who got raped.'
當發現懷孕的時候  我不想輟學
And when I became pregnant, I wasn't going to drop out of school.
我不想讓那個男人毀了我的生活
I wasn't going to let this man ruin my life.
所以我做出了決定  選擇墮胎
So I made a choice. I ended it.
但是如果你選擇保持沉默
But if you never told anybody about it,
罪犯可能還逍遙法外
the assailant could still be out there.
你能講講關於他的事嗎
Can you tell us anything about him?
就在幾個月前
I saw him, uh,
時隔三十年  我又見到了他
for the first time in almost 30 years just a few months ago.
在哪裡
Where?
在弗蘭西斯和我出席的授銜典禮上
At a commissioning ceremony that Francis and I attended.
你和他說話了嗎
You speak to him?
說了幾句  弗蘭西斯為他授銜
Briefly. Francis pinned stars on him.
他是授銜者嗎
He was being commissioned?
道頓·麥金尼斯將軍
General Dalton McGinnis.
我要聲明一下  弗蘭西斯知道那次強姦
And for the record, Francis has always known about the assault.
只是不知道名字
He just didn't know the name.
這些年來  他一直十分支援我
And he's been nothing but supportive all these years.
我們得和將軍取得聯繫
W—--w--we're gonna have to reach out to the General.
看看他對你的話作何迴應
for a response to what you just said.
請問我們能不能  稍事休息
Would you mind if we took a quick break?
當然
Absolutely.
稍後繼續克萊爾·安德伍德夫人的訪談
We'll be right back with Mrs. Claire Underwood.
不著急  慢慢來
Take all the time you need.
實驗室檢驗結果全是陰性  先生
The lab tests all came back negative, sir.
那玩意是什麼
What was it?
混了麵粉的滑石粉
Talcum powder laced with flour.
小麥裡的農藥讓檢測呈現假陽性
It was pesticide from the wheat that gave us the false positive.
那我們可以走了吧
So are we're free to go?
是的  先生
Yes, sir.
-南茜  告訴他們我這就下樓    -已經告知了
- Nancy, let them 'em I'm on my way down.   - I already did.
-不介意我用你的電話吧    -請便
- Mind if I use your phone?   - Of course.
還有  唐納德  我會幫你搞到研究資金的
And, Donald? I'm gonna get you that research funding,
無論投票結果如何
no matter how the vote goes.
-你自己看著辦  我還是會投反對票    -理解
- It's your call, because I'm still voting against it.   - I understand.
你妻子很勇敢  弗蘭克
You have a brave wife, Frank.
你妻子也是  唐納德
So do you, Donald.
弗蘭克
Frank!
你怎麼樣
How'd you do?
-還剩四個  布萊斯怎麼樣    -還是不讓步
- We're down to four. How about Blythe?   - He won't budge.
你給了他什麼好處
What did you offer him?
老年癡呆症的研究經費  他覺得這是侮辱
Alzheimer's research. He was insulted.
投票還有45分鐘就要開始了
The vote's in 45 minutes.
我得聯繫上克萊爾  上車後我該打給誰
I need to get to Claire. Who should I call from the car?
我們沒別的辦法了
We've exhausted our options.
不說服布萊斯那邊  就通不過投票
It's either Blythe's people, or it won't pass.
他們對他太忠心了
They're too loyal to him.
行  去吧  我來解決
Okay. Go. I'll figure it out.
如果需要我  我可以留下來
I can stay if you need me.
不用  去找你妻子  我知道去哪找你
No. Get to your wife. I know where to find you.
南茜  手頭所有的紙都給我  再找些推車
Nancy, I need every ream of paper you have. And get me dollies.
就快完成了  還有20分鐘
Almost done. Twenty more minutes.
我討厭撒謊
I hate lying.
-他做了那事嗎    -做了
- Did he do it?   - Yes.
那就別內疚
Then, don't feel bad.
要是他否認了呢
What if he denies it?
那就兵來將擋  水來土掩
Then we'll cross that bridge.
-康納    -再等一分鐘
- Connor?   - Give us one more minute.
有個年輕女人打電話來  是內線
We have a young woman on the phone, a private.
她說她也被將軍強姦了  兩年前
She says she was also assaulted by the General. Two years ago.
她想說出她的故事  但不肯透露姓名
She wants to share her story, but she won't give her name.
如果她不透露姓名  就不能報道
We can't put her on if she's anonymous.
-你想讓我說服她嗎    -她很害怕
- You want me to convince her?   - She's frightened.
她還線上上嗎
Is she still on the phone?
我沒和任何人說過
I've never told anyone.
我過了大半輩子  才有勇氣說起這件事
It took me almost half my life before I could say anything.
但你現在能說了
But you can say something now.
我不知道
I don't know.
想想還可能有多少其他受害者
Just think of how many others there must have been.
但你想讓我說出來
But you want me to talk.
如果你不想說  就不會打電話了
Well, would you have called if you didn't want to?
我沒想到還得公開姓名
I didn't think I'd have to use my name.
聽著  我理解你害怕後果
Listen, I understand you're afraid of the consequence.
我是個二等兵  而他是將軍
I'm a private. He's a general.
而我丈夫是美國副總統
And my husband is the Vice President of the United States.
我們會保護你  我向你保證
We will protect you. I promise you that.
你叫什麼名字
What's your name?
二等兵梅根·漢納希
Private Megan Hennessey.
這是什麼
What is this?
一旦開銷凍結
The names of every person in America
以下所有人就會失去家庭醫保
who will lose home care when the Freeze sets in,
失去一半的社會福利
who will lose half of their welfare benefits,
被強迫休假  失去學生貸款
who will go on furlough, who will lose their student loans,
交通服務  戰後創傷心理諮詢  還要我繼續嗎
transportation services, post-combat counseling. Shall I go on?
我們得為大局著想  傑奎琳
This is about the big picture, Jacqueline.
這個局面我覺得已經很大了
This picture looks pretty big to me.
我不能投贊成票
I can't vote for the package.
那就別投  你們中有四個人就行
Then don't. Just get four of your people to do it.
避免政府關門後跟我合作
And then work with me after we avoid the Freeze.
我不是弗蘭克·安德伍德
I'm not Frank Underwood.
那年至少還有另外兩個女孩
At least two other girls that same year.
如果屬實  那麼他服役的這些年來...
If that was true for all the years he's served...
太讓人震驚了
It's just staggering.
而且我覺得非常無助
And I felt so helpless.
然後他一直晉銜  受到體制的保護
And he keeps rising in the ranks. The system protects him.
你覺得為什麼從來沒有人告過他
Why do you think no one has ever reported him?
你想加入嗎
Do you wanna join her?
-我們知道根本沒用    -不想
- We know it won't do anything.      - No.
官大一級壓死人
Chain of command.
你願意出生入死地保衛我們的自由
It's inexcusable that you're willing to put your life on the line
然而你卻無法自由
to defend our freedom,
說出實情  這實在不可原諒
and yet you don't feel the freedom to come forward.
我熱愛我的國家
I love my country.
我也喜歡在海軍陸戰隊服役
And I love serving in the Marines.
但不是這樣的
But not like this.
二等兵漢納希  感謝你今晚如此勇敢  接受採訪
Private Hennessey, thank you for your courage in joining us this tonight.
是安德伍德夫人給了我勇氣
It was Mrs. Underwood who gave me the courage.
安德伍德夫人  也感謝你的坦誠
And, Mrs. Underwood, thank you, for your honesty.
長官  您夫人來電
Sir, your wife is on the phone.
你給了我們很多需要思考的東西
You've given all of us a great deal to think about.
謝謝你  阿什利
Thank you, Ashleigh.
與克萊爾·安德伍德的
And that concludes our live,
面對面獨家專訪到此結束
one-on-one exclusive interview with Claire Underwood.
您可以到我們的網站觀看完整的專訪
You can watch the entire interview on our website.
我們也歡迎您在臉譜網和推特上
And, as always, we invite you to give us your thoughts
與我們進行互動
and your comments on Facebook and on Twitter.
今天的專訪就到這兒  感謝收看  晚安
But, for now, thanks for watching. And good night.
結束
And we're out.
這會引起超出你想像的軒然大波
This is going to make waves like you never imagined.
謝謝
Thank you.
卡特呢
Where's Carter?
你現在向我彙報了
You'll be reporting to me now.
那你是誰
And who are you?
卡特的上司
Carter's boss.
嘉文  你幹得不錯
You're doing good work, Gavin.
但是你不能對目標動手  那可能會讓我們暴露
But you can't be assaulting the target. That could compromise us.
我都不知道為什麼我們要追查這個人
I don't even know why you're going after this guy.
他根本不入流
He's small-time.
這不是你的事
That's not your concern.
他連寫一行程式碼救自己的命都做不到
He couldn't write a line of code to save his life.
他想發動網路恐怖襲擊
He intends to commit an act of cyber terrorism.
那只是個想法  不是能力  他不是真正的威脅
Well, that's intention, not capability. He's not a real threat.
也許卡特會跟你好言相勸
Maybe Carter talked things out with you.
我不會的
I won't.
還要多久
How much longer?
什麼多久
Until what?
多久我才能收手
Until I can stop.
你更想進監獄嗎
Do you prefer prison?
我幫你抓到了八個兒童色情製作者
I've given you eight child pornographers,
三個僵屍網路病毒製造者
three botnet masters...
但是你還是沒有抓到AVunit
But you still haven't given us the AVunit.
我告訴卡特了  我不知道他在哪
Well, I told Carter I don't know where he is.
你知道
Yes, you do.
我不知道  誰也不知道
I don't. Nobody does.
那你在Dec-Sec的朋友呢
Then what about your friends in Dec-Sec?
我不會讓你動我朋友的
I'm not giving you my friends.
那你就幹這個吧  你是個很有用的線人  嘉文
Then you'll keep doing this. You're a productive asset, Gavin,
但等你沒用了  什麼律師也救不了你
but the moment you stop being productive, no lawyer can help you.
要是有根真的就好了
Wish we had the real thing right now.
時刻準備
Always prepared.
弗蘭西斯
Francis.
我真懷念這樣
I've missed this.
我也是
So have I.
你不應該去接電話  聽別人誇你嗎
Shouldn't you be on the phone getting your accolades?
明天也來得及
That can wait till tomorrow.
給我唱首歌吧
Sing me something.
你想聽什麼
What do you want to hear?
什麼都行
Anything.
*波莉  美麗的波莉*
*Polly, pretty Polly*
*你別覺得我無情*
*Would you take me unkind?*
*哦  波莉  美麗的波莉*
*Oh, Polly, pretty Polly*
*你別覺得我無情*
*Would you take me unkind?*
*讓我陪在你身旁*
*Let me set beside you*
*傾訴衷腸*
*And tell you my mind*
*我想和你在一起*
*Well, my mind is to marry*
*永不分離*
*And never to part*
*我想和你在一起*
*Well, my mind is to marry*
*永不分離*
*And never to part*
*初次見你*
*The first time I saw you*
*你讓我心傷*
*You wounded my heart*
*哦  波莉  美麗的波莉*
*Oh, Polly, pretty Polly*
*跟我走吧*
*Come go along with me*
*哦  波莉  美麗的波莉*
*Oh, Polly, pretty Polly*
*跟我走吧*
*Come go along with me*
*結婚之前*
*Before we get married*
*共享歡愉*
*Some pleasures to see*
*結婚之前*
*Before we get married*
*共享歡愉*
*Some pleasures to see*
■
2011年《新聞週刊》的一篇報道中指出
美國軍隊中女兵被戰友性侵的可能要大於在戰鬥中陣亡的可能性
2013年美國國防部的報告認為
美軍中每年發生性侵犯案例可能多達1萬9千宗
但只有1108名受害者報案
由於軍隊長官在軍內性侵案的調查上有極大的決定權力
所以極少施暴者會受到軍法處置
■
2013年媒體揭露美國空軍多起性侵案
同時也曝光了一些性侵案罪犯定罪後被主將赦免的案例
引起美國社會廣泛關注
美軍參謀長聯席會議主席德·摩西  國防部長海格
以及美國總統歐巴馬都在不同場合對這種現象進行了批判
在國會女性議員的主導下
美國國會在2013年年末通過了新的防止軍內性侵的法案
限制了軍隊長官對性侵案件的干涉